

BART GYSEN

• PERSONAL DETIALS •

Oude Liersebaan 113 2220 Heist-op-den-Berg 0471416082

bart-gysen@hotmail.com

Date / place of birth

19/09/1991

Maaseik

Nationality

Belgian

Driving license

В, С

• LINKS •

LinkedIn

Github

<u>Portfolio</u>

• REFERENCES •

Peter Van Grieken – Project Leader
Dekimo Turnhout
peter.vangrieken@dekimo.com
+32473452804

• PERSONAL SKILLS •

Go-getter

Teamplayer

Independent

Eager to learn

Creative

Flexibel

Enthusiastic

• LANGUAGES •

Dutch

English

PROFILE

After graduating and working for 10 years as an electrician in both domestic and industrial environments, I wanted to follow my passion and started studying Internet of Things at Thomas More in Geel. In addition to a focus on software development in C and Python, we covered several technologies during the course, including working with microcontrollers, single board computers, Linux and more.

As part of my studies, I carried out a number of projects to put my knowledge to the test. This included a project to read an energy meter using Modbus. The application/firmware would sent all the data to the data analysis tool using Debian for cross-compiling and remote debugging. I also did a project to read a thermostat using MQTT and another to learn FreeRTOS.

As an internship at Dekimo, I researched the new Matter protocol and built a controller that controls a game via Matter.

You can find these projects on my GitHub account.

* TECHNICAL SKILLS

C/C++

Very good

Python

Very good

Linux

Good

MS SQL

Good

Networking

Basic

HTML5

Basic

EDUCATION

Graduate Internet of Things (ICT), Thomas More Kempen, Geel

januari 2021 — June 2024

Electric Installations, GITHO, Nijlen

2008 - 2010

Electric Installations, T.I.M, Maasmechelen

2004 — 2007

○ HOBBIES ○

I enjoy working with computers and electronics, and I love turning my house into a smart home.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Internship R&D (Embedded Software), Dekimo, Turnhout

September 2023 — June 2024

Learn about the new Matter protocol and include it into a demo to attract an audience at trade shows. Learn about the new Matter protocol and include it into a demo to attract anaudience at trade shows. This project included a wide range of tasks, including creating my own schedule using a Gantt chart, working with prototypes, utilizing Linux, Python, C, and C++, as well as preparing a technical analysis to thoroughly support the project.

Service technician, Alertis, Lummen

April 2022 — Today

Maintenance, repair and installation of automatic fire and gas protection systems.

Technician electricity, Unit-T, Mechelen

October 2021 — April 2022

Installation of new digital electricity and gas meters.

Technician electricity, Electro Zwijsen, Duffel

 ${\sf March\,2021-October\,2021}$

Perform minor and major modifications to electrical installations, primarily in office buildings.

Technician high voltage electricity, Telcom, Hulshout

May 2016 — March 2021

Performing electrical work in and around high voltage cabinets.

Technician electricity, Goosens Electro, Hulshout

November 2015 — April 2016

Perform electrical work in the construction of new home and in renovation projects.

Technician high voltage electricity, Telcom, Hulshout

 ${\it April\,2011-October\,2015}$

Performing electrical work in and around high voltage cabinets.

Interim jobs

September 2010 — April 2011

Interim jobs in production and warehouses